{
    "id": "d1c6b6b4e8d94368be8866cedae0bb1f",
    "title": "As vs. Like",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is as beautiful ………………………. an angel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "89e84e56717942b3987150bee8a85bbc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The jewels shone ……………………….. stars.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is used before nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2445322954b4723a1c0cd710a76a6f9"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... you know, I am looking for a job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Like"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "12cb7b57a2044b01a8b2c2cddd395253"
        },
        {
            "question": "She talks …………………………. a scholar.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is used before nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8d6c8dfba0ec42d6987649781517faf4"
        },
        {
            "question": "They were fighting …………………………….. dogs.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is used before nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "266a6028170344cca6ed2f34a8e1d456"
        },
        {
            "question": "I felt ..................................... crying.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6983e0e52dbd42e4bb620bfce4f953f4"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. responsible citizens, we should abide by the rules and regulations.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Like"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d5df3bce5467414380e116c5ec3d85b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She looks ……………………….. Princess Diana.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is used before nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d1b9e63748a349f7b8755072b4b5f44c"
        },
        {
            "question": "It looks ................................... it is starting to rain.",
            "description": "Like is possible here in an informal style. ",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "as if",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eab86c09502e4345a99c3c7655d1335c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She talks .................................... she is rich.",
            "description": "As if is used to say how a particular situation seems like. ",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as if",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3128db8bc3c1455dbd1a308c8610e69f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He sat there crying .................................... he had lost everything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as if",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "302fe2001d3e492b9170ef6ac20dd38f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She sings …………………………… a nightingale.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is used before nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1d352b6b42d145098a7a719f831c5b33"
        }
    ]
}